cards:
  - question: "Is it raining?"
    answer: "क्या बारिश हो रही है?"
  - question: "Fountain"
    answer: "फव्वारा"
  - question: "Sunday"
    answer: "रविवार"
  - question: "Monday"
    answer: "सोमवार"
  - question: "Tuesday"
    answer: "मंगलवार"
  - question: "Wednesday"
    answer: "बुधवार"
  - question: "Thursday"
    answer: "गुरुवार"
  - question: "Friday"
    answer: "शुक्रवार"
  - question: "Saturday"
    answer: "शनिवार"
  - question: "black"
    answer: "काला"
  - question: "white"
    answer: "सफ़ेद"
  - question: "brown"
    answer: "भूरा"
  - question: "green"
    answer: "हरा"
  - question: "blue"
    answer: "नीला"
  - question: "grey"
    answer: "स्लेटी"
  - question: "red"
    answer: "लाल"
  - question: "yellow"
    answer: "पीला"
  - question: "purple"
    answer: "बैंगनी"
  - question: "pink"
    answer: "गुलाबी"
  - question: "orange"
    answer: "नारंगी"